Vida Chenoweth collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - Two Kundu songs, 1986-07-20, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/515 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR548)
    Papua New Guinea. Morobe Province. Contents: Laelo Village, Sio I language. Two songs Kundu. Music. Collected by Paul Grose and Peter Jorgenson. People/language group: Sio.
  - Papua New Guinea songs sung by Melikisede, 1986-07-22, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/516 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR549)
    Papua New Guinea. Morobe Province. Contents: Lambutina Village, Sio II language, Morobe Prov. Papua New Guinea songs sung by Melikisede. Music. Collected by Paul Grose and Peter Jorgenson. People/language group: Sio.
  - Sio Church and Sing-Sing, 1986-07-23, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/517 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR550)
    Papua New Guinea. Morobe Province. Contents: Lambatina village, Sio 2, Church and Sing-Sing. Lullabies. Music. Collected by Paul Grose and Peter Jorgenson. People/language group: Sio.
  - Kaulong Sing-Sing, 1986-06-14, 1 sound cassette, C90; C86/518 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR551)
    Papua New Guinea. West New Britain. Contents: Village Au Kaulong lang. Sing-Sing. Music. Collected by Kathy Saperstein. People/language group: Kaulong.
  - Duke of York songs, 1986-06-11, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/519 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR552)
    Papua New Guinea. Duke of York Islands. Contents: Duke of York language, East New Britain Province. Christian song text: Ro 5:8. Composer Isaac Alipet. Music and spoken word. Collected by Paul Grose. People/language group: Romaaina.
  - Mangseng music, 1986-06-15, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/520 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR553)
    Papua New Guinea. West New Britain. Contents: Lavege Village. New Material: Vuncungong Category. Music. Collected by Paul Grose. People/language group: Mangseng.
  - Ninam men's music, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/521 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR554)
    Brazil. Roraima. Contents: Ninam Men's Music, Camargo. Collected by Carole Swain and Milton Camargo. Music. People/language group: Ninam.
  - Yaimo songs, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/522 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR555)
    Brazil. Roraima. Contents: Yaimo Songs. Collected by Carole Swain and Milton Camargo. Music. People/language group: Ninam.
  - Ninam songs, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/523 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR556)
    Brazil. Roraima. Contents: Ninam songs. Collected by Carole Swain and Milton Camargo. Sound Recording Log. People/language group: Ninam. Original home recording.
  - Women's conference singing, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/524 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR557)
    Zaire. Kasai Province. Contents: Women's conference singing. Music and spoken word. Collected by elsbeth Shannon. People/language group: Tshiluba. Original home recording.
  - Music and spoken word from Duke of York Islands, ca. 1985, 1 sound cassette, C90; C85/525 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR558)
    Papua New Guinea. East New Britain. Contents: Villages of Palipal and Nagaila on Makada Islands in the Duke of York Islands. Music and spoken word. Collected by LaMoyne Schneider. Interpreter, Danks Ekonia from Nagaila. People/language group: Romaaina.
  - Dida sound recording log, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/527 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR560)
    Ivory Coast. Yocoboue village. Contents: Sound Recording Log. People/language group: Dida. Original home recording.
  - Mali church music, 1986-08, 1 sound cassette; C86/528 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR561)
    Mali. Contents: Segou city, church music. Music. Recorded by the congregation. Gift from Jeff Becker. People/language group: Bambara. Original home recording.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1963, 1 sound tape reel; C63/531 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR564)
    Collected by Joy McCarthy.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel; C65/532 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR565)
  - Pajonal Campa songs and stories, 1974-05, 1 sound cassette; C86/533 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR566)
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-07, 1 sound cassette; C86/534 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR567)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Tsirentsishavo village.Tape # 14. Drink song sung by Oscar. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs and stories, 1977-02, 1 sound cassette; C86/535 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR568)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Majontonini village. Tape 14b. Quechua Quena (Cowanito), panpipes (Choviri), duet sung by Choviri, Cowanito. Stories by Leopoldo and Celinda. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/536 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR569)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Tape 6. Drinking, animal, bird, fish, frog, pet songs sung by Cesario 36-41. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/537 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR570)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Tsirentsishavo village. Tape 7. Drinking, animal, nature, love songs sung by Irocarto, Valerio. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/538 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR571)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Tsirentsishavo village. Tape 8. Drinking, animal, lullaby, courting songs sung by Irocarto, Oncavo. 1-17. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-07, 1 sound cassette; C86/539 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR572)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Tsirentsishavo village. Tape 13. Trade, drinking, women, father, arrow, animal songs sung by Oscar, Rosiya. 1-11. Sound of arrow, laughing. 9-11. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/540 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR573)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Tape 16. Animal, bird, chopping tree, cutting trail songs sung by Cesario 1-10. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/541 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR574)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Tape 2. Men's song, love, marrige, rain, earthquake, songs sung by Cesario 11-15. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/542 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR575)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Tape 3. Drink, stars, trade, exhortation songs sung by Cesario 22-31. Sound recording log. Collected by D. Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/543 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR576)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Shomavani, Pauonal Campa language. Tape 4. Drink songs, lullaby sung by Shinongama and Felipe, Inquivi, Piyavo, Coshantshi Shiyava, Martin from Shinchari. 1-23. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/544 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR577)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Pauonal Campa language. Tape 15. Drink songs, Drinking, animal, bird songs sung by Cesario, Elena, Anita, Raquel #31-36, 42-54. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/545 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR578)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Tsirentsishavo village. Tape 17. Drinking, nature, animal, preparing garden songs sung by Valerio, Margariya, Elena, Intaneri. 13-24. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/546 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR579)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Tape 10. Planting, animal, wife, pet songs sung by Cesario, Intaneri. 41, 1-9. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/547 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR580)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village. Collector D Shaler. Tape 11. Pet, wife, drinking, bird songs sung by Intaneri, Cesario. 1-13. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Pajonal Campa songs, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/548 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR581)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Chequitavo village, Collector Dorothy Shaler. Tape 12. Animal/bird, drinking, trading songs sung by Elena/Cesario. 1-10. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Pajonal Campa. Original home recording.
  - Nahua song, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/549 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR582)
    Peru. Atalaya. Contents: Mishagua River, South of Yarinacoha. One song by Chiaka. Sound recording log. Collected by Dorothy Shaler. People/language group: Nahua. Original home recording.
  - African church music, Zaire, 1983-04-24, 1 sound cassette; C86/550 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR583)
    Zaire. West Kasai. Contents: Tshiluba. West Kasai language. African church music. Presbyterian Church of Kamilabi, Kananga. Collected by Elisabeth Shannon. Rev. Mpongo's ordination. Music. Collected by Elisabeth Shannon. Pepole/language group: Tshiluba.
  - Christian songs from Rotokas, 1986-07, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/551 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR584)
    Papua New Guinea. North Solomons. Contents: Togarao village, Totokas language. Bongainville Island. Christian songs from Rotokas. Music literacy. Sound Recording Log. People/language group: Rotokas. Original home recording.
  - Dance songs, Zaire, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/552 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR585)
    Zaire. Kasai Province. Contents: Tsuikete, dance songs. Bakete - Bausueba Language. Music. People/language group: Tshikete. Original home recording.
  - Tsuikete songs, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/553 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR586)
    Zaire. Kasai Province. Contents: Tsuikete, songs of ancestors. Bulape, people. Bakete - Bausueba Language. Music. Collected by Elisabeth Shannon. People/language group: Tshikete. Original home recording.
  - Madagascar instrumental music, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/554 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR587)
    Ethiopia, Madagascar (Malagasy), Reunion Island, Togo. Contents: Madagascar (southern region) instrumental, misc. Sound Recording Log. Collected by Joyce Henry. Original home recording.
  - Mangseng Sing-Sing, 1986-06, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/555 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR588)
    Papua New Guinea. West New Britain. Contents: Lavege village. Mangseng language. Sing-Sing. Sound Recording Log. Collected by Paul Grose. People/language group: Mangseng. Original home recording.
  - Baining scripture verses and interview with Mary Karekses, 1985-06, 1 sound cassette; C86/556 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR589)
    Papua New Guinea. West New Britain. Contents: Potpotpua village. Interviewing Mary Karekses. Collected by Paul Grose. Baining Scripture verses. Joel Karekses Jn. 3:3a. Interviewing Mary Karekses. Recorded by Susan Richardson and Vida Chenoweth. People/language group: Mangseng. Original home recording.
  - Adioukrou, sound recording log, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/557 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR590)
    Ivory Coast. Contents: S.I.L. Sound Recording Log. Collected by Harriet Hill. People/language group: Adioukrou. Original home recording.
  - Angor sound recording log, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette; C86/558 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR591)
    Papua New Guinea. West Sepik. Collected by R. Litteral. People/language group: Angor. Sound Recording Log. Original home recording.
  - "African Folk Music Regenerated: A New Church Music", 1985-12-10, 1 sound cassette; C86/559 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR592)
    Zaire. Contents: Chorale Nentume Nganyi C.P. Za Tshikapa - ETAT ESAIE 6:8. Shannon, Elisabeth "African Folk Music Regenerated: A New Church Music." Wheaton, Illinois. Collected by Elisabeth Shannon. People/language group: Otetela, Tshiluba, Lingale, French, Kasai, Uruund, Bushongo, Pende. Original home recording.
  - "African Folk Music Regenerated: A New Church Music", 1985, 1 sound cassette; C86/560 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR593)
    Zaire. Kazadis Choir. Contents: Shannon, Elisabeth "African Folk Music Regenerated: A New Church Music." Wheaton, Illinois. People/language group: Otetela, Tshiluba, Lingale, French, Kasai, Uruund, Bushongo, Pende. Original home recording.
  - Lirrga songs, 1983-03-10, 1 sound cassette; C86/561 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR594)
    Australia. Northern Territory. Contents: Port Keats. Lirrga songs. Music. Collected by C. Street. People/language group: Maringarr. Original home recording.
  - African church music, 1986-1987, 1 sound cassette; C86/562 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR595)
    Zaire. East and West Kasai. Contents: Village of Bibanga and city of Kananga. African church music. Music. Collected by Elisabeth Shannon. People/language group: Tshiluba, Lingala and French. Original home recording.
  - Ethnomusicology student comps and document recital, 1987-01-19, 1 sound cassette; C87/563 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR596)
    Papua New Guinea. West New Britain. Contents: Ethnomusicology student comps. In 4 PNG music systems. Student Paul Grose giving document recital. Sound Recording Log. Collected by Paul Grose. People/language group: Mangseng Baining, Kol, Halia. Original home recording.
  - Duke of York Islands sound recording log, 1985, 1 sound cassette; C85/564 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR597)
    Papua New Guinea. Duke of York Islands. Contents: Palipal and Nagaila villages. Sound Recording Log. Collected by LaMoyne Schneider. People/language group: Romaaina. Original home recording.
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1966, 1 sound tape reel; R66/565 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR598)
  - Lae show, 1966, 1 sound cassette; R66/565a (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR599)
  - Lae show, 1966, 1 sound cassette; R66/565a (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR600)
    Papua New Guinea. Lae Show. Collected by Vida Chenoweth. People/language group: Banale, Asaro, Kemen, Bundim Kaabwum, Tufi, Bena Bena, etc.
  - Angor sound recording log, 1984-03, 1 sound cassette; C84/566 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR602)
    Papua New Guinea. West Sepik Province. Contents: Amanab District. Biwan village. Sound Recording Log. Collected by G. James. People/language group: Angor. Original home recording.
  - Yale - Kosarek music, 1987-03, 1 sound cassette; C87/567 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR603)
    Contents: Yale - Kosarek. Music. Collected by Duane Clouse with Richard Steinbring. People/language group: Yale-Kosarek. Original home recording.
  - Kosarek music, 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/568 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR604)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Kosarek music. Church service. Sound recording log. Collected by Richard Steinbring. People/language group: Yale-Met. Original home recording.
  - Kosarek music, 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/569 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR605)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Kosarek music. Church service. Sound recording log. Collected by Richard Steinbring. People/language group: Yale. Original home recording.
  - Mairasi day and night songs, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/570 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR606)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: District of Fapfak (in Bird's Neck), sub-district: Kaimana. Lobo village. Day and night songs. Collector: Lloyd Peckham. Sound recording log. People/language group: Mairasi. Original home recording.
  - Abun song text and sound recording log, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/571 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR607)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: North Bird's Head. Collector: Keith Berry. Song Text, Sound Recording Log. People/language group: Abun. Original home recording.
  - Sentani, Akoi-koi songs and dances, 1986-06-05, 1 sound cassette; C87/572 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR608)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Sentani, Itakiwa/Ayapo village. S.I.L. Content: Susundo, Alo Yalei-Yalei, Obo Mandu, Akoi-koi (songs and dances). Collected by Duane Clouse. Sound recording log. People/language group: Sentani. Original home recording.
  - Kanang songs, 1986, 1 sound cassette; C87/573 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR609)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Kanang songs. Tape 2 of 2. Collected by Phil Fields. Sound recording log. People/language group: Orya. Original home recording.
  - Boyo songs, 1986, 1 sound cassette; C87/574 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR610)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Boyo songs. Tape 1 of 2. Collected by Phil Fields. Sound recording log. People/language group: Orya. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, 1982-1983, 1 sound cassette, C90; C87/575 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR611)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Yakkumo incomplete. Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, 1982, 1 sound cassette, C90; C82/575 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR612)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Angoya music II, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/576 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR613)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Wefaiyo (from Kamea language group). Angoya Music II. Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/576 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR614)
  - Angoya music III, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/577 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR615)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Angoya Music III. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/577 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR616)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Kamea language group, 1983-1984, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/578 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR617)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Tepio (ancestor songs from the neighboring Kamea language group), Pamaini, Etoma (oyme), Tio, Etoma (aytki), Tepio, Yakkumo (aytki). Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/578 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR618)
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/579 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR619)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Wetoyo 00-23, Nathan Whitney 29-121, Pemaini 123-end. Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/579 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR620)
  - Akoye sound recording log, volume 6, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/580 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR621)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Vol. 6. Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1983, 1 sound cassette, C60; C83/580 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR622)
  - Akoye sound recording log, volume 7, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/581 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR623)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Flute and Jews harp. Vol.7. Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1986, 1 sound cassette, C60; C86/581 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR624)
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1985, 1 sound cassette, C60; C85/582 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR625)
  - Akoye sound recording log, volume 8, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/582 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR626)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Yinki. Vol. 8. Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, volume 9, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette, C60; C87/583 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR627)
    Papua New Guinea. Gulf Province. Contents: Good tyti. Vol. 9. Sound recording log. People/language group: Akoye. Original home recording.
  - Akoye sound recording log, ca. 1997, 1 sound cassette, C60; C97/583 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR628)
  - Asmat songs, 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/584 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR629)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Ayam village. Asmat songs. Songs 1-9. Sound recording log. Collected by Calvin Roessler. People/language group: Asmat. Original home recording.
  - Asmat songs, 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/585 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR630)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Ayam village. Ayam village. Asmat songs #2. Songs 10-15. Sound recording log. Collected by Calvin Roessler. People/language group: Asmat. Original home recording.
  - Makak sound recording log, 1987-06, 1 sound cassette; C87/586 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR631)
    Cameroon. Contents: Ewando children. Sound recording log. Collected by Joan Baumberger. People/language group: Makak. Original home recording.
  - Yali children's songs, 1986-11, 1989-12-15, 1 sound cassette; C87/587 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR632)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Yali Children's Songs. Sound recording log. Michelotti, Gioia and Jean Williams "A Preliminary Analysis of Yali Song. From a Selected Corpus of the Yali People Irian Jaya, Indonesia." Wheaton, Illinois. December 15, 1989. Collected by Molly Hewitt and Heljia Heikenen with Duane Clouse. People/language group: Yali. Original home recording.
  - Otetela content from Kasai province, tape 4, 1987-02, 1 sound cassette; C87/588 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR633)
    Zaire. Kasai oriental province. Contents: Tape #4. Collected by Elisabeth Shannon. People/language group: Otetela language. Original home recording.
  - Uruund content from Shaba province, tape 4, 1986-12, 1 sound cassette; C87/589 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR634)
    Zaire. Shaba province. Contents: Tape #3. Collected by Elisabeth Shannon. People/language group: Uruund language. Original home recording.
  - Sound recording log, Bassar Tog area, ca. 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/590 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR635)
    Ethiopia, Madagascar (Malagasy), Reunion Island, Togo. Contents: Bassar Tog Area. Sound recording log. Collected by Paul Meier. Original home recording.
  - Lau music, 1980-12, 1 sound cassette; C87/591 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR636)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Ian Jaw's harp. Flutes. Singing. Sound recording log. Collected by Janet Bateman. People/language group: Lau. Original home recording.
  - Makak music, 1984, 1 sound cassette; C87/592 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR637)
    Cameroon. Yaounde Zone. Ndzong Mele. Contents: Balafons (xylophones). Sound recording log. Collected by Emmanuel Njock. People/language group: Makak. Original home recording.
  - Irian Jaya music, 1987, 1 sound cassette; C87/594 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR639)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: 1. Wane (version II), 2. Pnurunan Hiasan (II), 3. Uringgau (II). Jayapura, Jayapura Kabupaten (Regency), Nimboran, Kemtuik and Gresi songs. Sound recording log. Collected by Fieje Duim. People/language group: Kemtuik Nimboran Gresi. Original home recording.
  - Dani and Ngalik sound recording log, 1986, 1 sound cassette; C87/595 (Tape-id AFC 1994/003: SR640)
    Indonesia. Irian Jaya. Contents: Tulem village. Silimo village. Grand Central Danis, Tulem. Sound recording log. Collected by Eric Maxey. People/language group: Dani and Ngalik. Original home recording.